export default [
    {
        "id":1,
        "question":"Javascript is an ______ language ?",
        "choices":["Object-Oriented", "Object-Based", "Procedural", "None of the above"],
        "answer":"Object-Oriented"
    },
    {
        "id":2,
        "question":"Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javscript ?",
        "choices":["var", "let", "Both A and B", "None of the above"],
        "answer":"Both A and B"
    },
    {
        "id":3,
        "question":"How do we write a comment in javscript?",
        "choices":["/**/", "//", "#", "$$"],
        "answer":"//"
    },
    {
        "id":4,
        "question":"What will be the output of the following code snippet: print(typeof(NaN); ?",
        "choices":["object", "Number", "String", "None of the above"],
        "answer":"Number"
    },
    {
        "id":5,
        "question":"JSON stands for what?",
        "choices":["Javascript Object Notation",
        "Java Script Number",
        "JavaScript Script Notice",
        "JavaScript Script Note"],
        "answer":"un langage informatique"
    },
    {
        "id":6,
        "question":"How to declare a variable in js ?",
        "choices":["let", "echo", "print", "console.log()"],
        "answer":"let"
    },
    {
        "id":7,
        "question":"which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using JavaScript ?",
        "choices":[ "getElementbyId()",
        "getElementbyClassName()",
        "Both A and B",
        "None of the above"],
        "answer":"Both A and B"
    },
    {
        "id":8,
        "question":"What keywords is used to chek whether a given property is valid or not ?",
        "choices":["in", "is in", "xists", "lies"],
        "answer":"in"
    },
    {
        "id":9,
        "question":"How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type ?",
        "choices":["cont", "var", "let", "constant"],
        "answer":"const"
    },
    {
        "id":10,
        "question":"Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript ?",
        "choices": [
            "document.writer()",
            "console.log()",
            "window.alert()",
            "all of the above",
          ],
        "answer":"all of the above"
    },
    {
        "id":11,
        "question":"Upon encountering empty statements, what does the Javascript interpreter do?",
        "choices":["Throws an error", "Ignores the statements", "Gives a warning", "None of the above"],
        "answer":"Ignores the statements"
    },
    {
        "id":12,
        "question":"What keywords is used to chek whether a given property is valid or not ?",
        "choices":["in", "is in", "xists", "lies"],
        "answer":"in"
    },
    {
        "id":13,
        "question":"What keywords is used to chek whether a given property is valid or not ?",
        "choices":["in", "is in", "xists", "lies"],
        "answer":"in"
    },
    {
        "id":14,
        "question":"What keywords is used to chek whether a given property is valid or not ?",
        "choices":["in", "is in", "xists", "lies"],
        "answer":"in"
    },
    {
        "id":15,
        "question":"What keywords is used to chek whether a given property is valid or not ?",
        "choices":["in", "is in", "xists", "lies"],
        "answer":"in"
    }
]